[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Who do they think you think instinctively go beat Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I don't think they know the answer to that question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "I mean, do you think that somebody like Michele Bachmann or Sarah Palin could ever actually win an election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann", "Sarah Palin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "At the moment, in the next few years in this country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Or does the rather intransigent streak that they bring to all that policy-making, is that always going to be the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "It's always going to be the problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Has he been disappointing or simply was it that expectation levels were way too high?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, I think the answer is both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "Has he got it in him, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I think he has it in him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Elmer Gantry"]}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "I mean, bordering on Joel Olsteen stuff, Frank?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Yes, a little Elmer Gantry thrown in.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel Olsteen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 201, "question": "I mean, is he somebody who could have his day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "I'm getting a sense that although he said to me absolutely no way am I going to run in 2012, he is coming under pressure, do you think from Republicans to chuck his hat in the ring?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "I think he has to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2012"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "What's your assessment of where the spoils of victory and defeat have worked themselves out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "ICH: Well, a few good things can be said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Do you subscribe to any of that theory?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "How do you intend to commemorate it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "I'm going to be quietly in New York.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Why are you one of Oprah's favorite things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I didn't realize you could give away a person on that show.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oprah"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "What was so special about you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Look, as me, if it were me, and it is, I have always scratched my head about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Have you ever used Josh Groban music?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I wish that I could use my own music in the same kind of way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Josh Groban"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Would there be someone you were thinking of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Oh, there is always a muse.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "What is the bad-ass?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "The bad-ass.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "You ever been a hopeless drunk, a drug addict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Never done any drugs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Are you a fighter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "I'm a control freak.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Do you like it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I do love it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Can you do it with anyone's?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "POS", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "I've been asked in the past and I've politely turned it down, just because you can't top that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "You've never slept with a groupie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "No, I haven't because I'm weird.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Who was it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "ORGAN: They won't complain, because it's obviously like a badge of honor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Have you interviewed Kid Rock?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "You want to share with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Not at the moment, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Do you ever sing to your ladies?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Find Your Light Foundation"]}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 593, "question": "What is it now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "It's now called the Find Your Light Foundation, which is to me how I felt --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "How can people help if they want to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "If they want to, they can visit my website, which is FindYourLightFoundation.org.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "Can you give me one last burst of \"Raise Me Up\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "You raise me up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "Are you trying to say I need to have a baby?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "I didn't even ask the question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Can we expect the little patter of little Beyonce and Jay-Zs?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Only God knows.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beyonce"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110901pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Would you mind asking him to tell me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "I will.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]